pickupflowers.com 2016-11-26

# Privacy Policy of Pickupflowers gives highest importance to the private information of the browsers.

**Pickupflowers** is committed to protecting your privacy. We collect your personal information that you voluntarily provide to us while using our Web site features. **Your privacy is important to us** and we do not share your information with any third-party.

  * When you visit our website, we may request and collect your contact information, which is voluntarily given by you. We use your Personally Identifiable Information for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration, informing you of our new products, services and offers.
  * When you visit our Site, we also collect some basic non-personally identifiable information about you. Such information includes visitor data relating to referring domains, the type of browsers used, operating system software (e.g. Windows 95 vs. 98), screen resolutions, color capabilities, plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. All this information is collected in order to provide you with better and satisfactory service and cannot be used to identify you in any way.
  * The circumstances under which we disclose Personal Information to third parties - **We never disclose any of your information to third parties**. Period.
  * How we protect your Personal Information? - **We use a high grade encryption (256 bit) to protect your information** when it is transmitted across computers. Please go through our security policy for more details. 

**Remarketing**  
Pickupflowers.com also uses 3rd party vendor re-marketing tracking cookies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie. This means we will continue to show ads to you across the internet, specifically on the Google Content Network (GCN). As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s or any other 3rd party remarketing system. The third-party vendors, will place cookies on web browsers in order to serve ads based on past visits to our website. Third party vendors, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. This allows us to make special offers and continue to market our services to those who have shown interest in our service. 

**Opt-Out**  
You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager. Also, you can opt out of other third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page. 

We believe in reducing the SPAM on the Internet and would not be sending you any marketing material unless you specifically request for it.

This Privacy Policy explains our privacy practices and informs you regarding:

You could E-Mail us at , if you have any concerns on your privacy being breached by us. You could also reach us through information provided on Contact Us page.

What are you shopping for?
